<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Scene Editor on Taleworlds Documentation</title>
    <link>http://localhost:4444/editor/scene-editor/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Scene Editor on Taleworlds Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://localhost:4444/editor/scene-editor/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Creating Entity</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4444/editor/scene-editor/creating_entity/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:4444/editor/scene-editor/creating_entity/</guid>
      <description>Game Entities are basic building blocks of Scenes. Every mesh, light, decal, script behaviour are components of entities. \
Creating an empty entity In the editor, you can begin by creating a new, empty entity by using the Add Empty Entitybutton from tool bar, then you can attach different components for different needs.
All entities can be composed of multiple components.
Adding Component Component can be added from the toolbar after selecting an entity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Editor Shortcuts</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4444/editor/scene-editor/editor_shortcuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:4444/editor/scene-editor/editor_shortcuts/</guid>
      <description>   General Editor Usage Shortcut Editor State     Show/hide helpers H Any mode   New scene Alt + 1 Any mode   Save scene Alt + 2 Any mode   Open scene Alt + 3 Any mode   Start mission Alt + 4 Any mode   Start mission as Alt + 5 Any mode   Scene Options Alt + 6 Any mode   Terrain Options Alt + 7 Terrain select   Terrain Elevation Alt + 8 Terrain Paint Elevate   Terrain Paint Alt + 9 Terrain Paint Paint   Shift between relevant 2 editor modes (select-add, select-elevatepaint etc) Space Any mode   Undo/Redo Ctrl+Z, Ctrl+Y Any mode       Camera Controls Shortcut Editor State     Focus on selected entity F Entity Select   Editor camera orbiting mode Alt (Hold) + Right Mouse Button Entity Select   Pan Alt (Hold) + Middle Mouse Button Entity Select   Zoom in/out Alt (Hold) + Mouse scroll wheel Entity Select   Camera speed increase/decrease Ctrl + Mouse scroll wheel Any mode   Camera speed set to 1 Ctrl + Middle mouse button Any mode       Prefab transform Shortcut Editor State     Rotate while placing Z, X, C, T, reset to default with R Entity Add   Move entity with placing on terrain Hold P Entity Select   Move entity vertically Hold N Entity Select   Move entity on the XY plane Hold G Entity Select   Show translate triad T Entity Select   Show rotating triad R Entity Select   Show scaling triad Y Entity Select   Duplicate the entity dragging on the translate triad Shift+Click or Shift+Drag to side Entity Select   Hide any triad on selected entity V Entity Select   Triads shown based on local coordinates (default) Alt+L Entity Select   Triads shown based on world coordinates Alt+W Entity Select   Material of an object under mouse opens in material editor (or material comes to inspector) M+Click Entity Select       Terrain Shortcut Editor State     Select all terrain nodes Ctrl + A Terrain Select   Lower when rise selected Alt + Click Terrain Paint Elevate   Rise when lower selected Alt + Click Terrain Paint Elevate   Flatten when Rise or Lower selected Ctrl + Left Mouse Click Terrain Paint Elevate   Smoothen when Rise or Lower selected Shift + Click Terrain Paint Elevate   Transfer height value to Flatten (when flatten selected) Alt + Click Terrain Paint Elevate   Flora paint (Not from layers) Left Mouse Click Entity Paint   Resize currently selected flora B (hold) + Mouse drag left/right Entity Paint   Place 1 flora (flora seen on brush) Ctrl + Left Mouse Click Entity Paint       Navmesh hotkeys Shortcut Editor State     Fill in closest 4 vertices (creates a quad) Shift + Click Navigation Mesh Add   Fill in the last 4 vertices (creates a quad) Ctrl + Space Navigation Mesh Add   Move vertex without selecting Ctrl + Drag Navigation Mesh Add   Delete face with mouse over (leaves vertices) Alt + Click Navigation Mesh Add   Delete face and remove all vertices Alt + X + Click Navigation Mesh Add   Selection mode - vertex 1 Navigation Mesh Select   Selection mode - edge 2 Navigation Mesh Select   Selection mode - face 3 Navigation Mesh Select   Select all vertices, edges or face (depends on the current selection) Ctrl + A Navigation Mesh Select   Delete selected vertices, edges or face Delete Navigation Mesh Select    </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Navmesh</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4444/editor/scene-editor/nav_mesh/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:4444/editor/scene-editor/nav_mesh/</guid>
      <description>What is the Navigation Mesh? Navigation Mesh is a compilation of models created by the scene designer for the use of AI to make sure they can move around without colliding with the physic objects in the scene. What are the important rules for Navigation Mesh? a. 1,5 Meter Rule: Designers needs to arrange the navigation mesh in a 1.5-meter diameter when creating on terrain or other objects that can be walked on or can stand on (Rooftops, castle walls etc.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Path Editing</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4444/editor/scene-editor/path_editing/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:4444/editor/scene-editor/path_editing/</guid>
      <description>Level designer can easily add, edit or delete paths and path points by the scene editor.
Adding a new path User can use the Add New Path button at the upper toolbar. User should enter a unique name for every path. After the path is added, the editor&amp;rsquo;s editing state will become &amp;ldquo;Path Select&amp;rdquo;. By spacing either space or the &amp;ldquo;Add a new path point&amp;rdquo; button from the upper toolbar, user can transition to the &amp;ldquo;Path Node Add&amp;rdquo; mode and start adding new path nodes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terrain Creation</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4444/editor/scene-editor/terrain_creation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:4444/editor/scene-editor/terrain_creation/</guid>
      <description>Create a new terrain Terrain creation, removal, and node modifications can be done in Terrain Inspector &amp;gt; Propertiestab. Terrain node count in both dimensions, their resolution and size can be specified in New Terrain Propertiespanel.This parameters must be specified proir to the creation, although they can be canged per-node basis later.
              Adjusting node properties Node resolution can be adjusted by selection nodes (Hold CTRL for multiple selection)m and change the resolution parameter in Node Propertiespanel.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Entity Inspector</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4444/editor/scene-editor/entity_inspector/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:4444/editor/scene-editor/entity_inspector/</guid>
      <description>Transform Panel Transform panel allows you to change position, rotation and scale properties of the selected entities. All of these values are relative to the parent of the selected entity. If Entity has no parent, then they are the Global values. (in Worldspace).
Scale Locked If the lock icon is in locked state, changing any component of scale parameter will set all scale components to the same value, entity will be in uniform scaling mode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Navigation Mesh Inspector</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4444/editor/scene-editor/nav_mesh_inspector/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:4444/editor/scene-editor/nav_mesh_inspector/</guid>
      <description>Tools These tools help you to generate and manipulate the navigation mesh:
Generation Tools  Auto Generate: As the name implies, automatically generates the navigation mesh with resppect to the parameters above. Generate Grids: Generates grid navigation mesh for the terrain only. It ignores the entities on the scene. Create New Face: Creates a new navigation mesh quad face on the coordinates where the camera is. Extrude: Remove: Removes the selected navigation mesh edge.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Alignment and Snapping Tools</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4444/editor/scene-editor/alignment_and_snapping/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:4444/editor/scene-editor/alignment_and_snapping/</guid>
      <description>Pivot Alignment Tool The Pivot alignment toolapplies the chosen transform values of one entity to another entity. The tool makes it easier for users to create overlapping or precisely aligned entities. If an entitity is selected in the editor, the user can set up the alignment tool by pressing Alt + A.This will register the currently selected entity as the input entity. Selecting a second entity with the left mouse button, will then open the interface screen of the alignment tool.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Distance Tool</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4444/editor/scene-editor/distance_tool/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:4444/editor/scene-editor/distance_tool/</guid>
      <description>Distance Measure Tool The Distance Toolmeasures the distance between two points in the scene. Distance measure mode can be activated by either pressing Alt + Dshortcut or the respective button on the editor toolbar.
While holding the left mouse button, drag the mouse between two points in the scene to measure distance. The tool snaps to vertices if close enough to a one by default, holding down Left Shiftoverrides this.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mass Selection</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4444/editor/scene-editor/mass_selection/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:4444/editor/scene-editor/mass_selection/</guid>
      <description>Mass Selection script allows you to select objects in a box and apply random rotations to selected objects. You can relocate and resize the selection box with translating, rotating and scaling entity which has &amp;ldquo;mass_selection&amp;rdquo; script. Bounding Box Constraint property allows you to select objects which has smaller bounding box than it&amp;rsquo;s value.
   Locate Selection Box After Select Objects After Apply Random Rotations           </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Precomputed Radiance Transfer - GI System</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4444/editor/scene-editor/prt/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:4444/editor/scene-editor/prt/</guid>
      <description>We introduce a new global illumination system to the engine. It is based on a pre-baked system called &amp;ldquo;Precomputed Radiance Transfer&amp;rdquo;. This technique allow us to bake the local ambient in the scene and display it in an optimized manner at runtime. Baked data is independent from the atmospheres. Thus, we can light the scene with the same bake data for every atmosphere.
   With Without          Baking Procedure Scene baking is divided into a couple of parts:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Resizing Terrain</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4444/editor/scene-editor/terrain_resize/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:4444/editor/scene-editor/terrain_resize/</guid>
      <description>Resizing Terrain If required, terrain node count can be resized at Resize Terrainpanel in Terrain Inspector.
 There are 4 direction that you can add new nodes, or remove existing nodes. +X, +Y, -X, -Y (South, East, North, West, respectively) (Coloring is consistent with Gizmo). \ Adding or removing nodes will automatically relocate existing entities and floras to their new locations. New nodes will have their height data unspecified, and may look unconnected to the rest of the terrain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Scene Level System</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4444/editor/scene-editor/level_system/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:4444/editor/scene-editor/level_system/</guid>
      <description>Level System New level system replaces the old, hardcoded system with a much more extandable and unified system. \
Addinga new level (or deletingan existing one) to a scene can be done in Levelspanel under SceneOptionsinspector.
Levels in Game - Bannerlord - Currently, Bannerlord recognizes a few levels that has a meaning in-game. \
Which are: \
 level_1 \ level_2 \ level_3 \ siege \ civilian  Setting Entity visibilities Making an entity only visible in a certain level combinations can be done with selecting an entity then going in Scene Level Visibilitiespanel under Entity Inspector.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terrain Mesh Blend System</title>
      <link>http://localhost:4444/editor/scene-editor/terrain_mesh_blend/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://localhost:4444/editor/scene-editor/terrain_mesh_blend/</guid>
      <description>We introduce a new terrain mesh blending system. Certain terrain layers can blend into chosen meshes. Blend height, smoothness and random height offsets can be changed. These values can be saved to prefabs and can also be changed in scene per mesh. Heightmap blending can also be used to change the blending behaviour with respect to the mesh&amp;rsquo;s heightmap.
   With Blending Without Blending          Terrain Layer Restrictions Terrain layers should satisfy some restrictions before they are eligible to be a mesh blend layer.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
